export default data = [
    {
        question: "Lost and scared, the little dog ______ along the streets, looking for its master",
        options: ["dismissed","glided","wandered","marched"],
        correct_option: "wandered"
    },
    {
        question: "On a sunny afternoon last month, we all took off our shoes and walked on the grass with _____ feet",
        options: ["bare","raw","tough","slippery"],
        correct_option: "bare"
    },
    {
        question: "It is both legally and _______ wrong to spread rumors about other people on the Internet",
        options: ["morally","physically","literarily","commercially"],
        correct_option: "morally"
    },
    {
        question: "These warm-up exercises are designed to help people _____ their muscles and prevent injuries",
        options: ["produce","connect","broaden","loosen"],
        correct_option: "loosen"
    },
    {
        question: "Mei-ling has a very close relationship with her parents. She always ______ them before she makes important decisions",
        options: ["impresses","advises","consults","motivates"],
        correct_option: "consults"
    },
    {
        question: "The restaurant has a _____ charge of NT$250 per person. So the four of us need to pay at least NT$1,000 to eat there",
        options: ["definite","minimum","flexible","numerous"],
        correct_option: "minimum"
    },
    {
        question: "At the Book Fair, exhibitors from 21 countries will _______ textbooks, novels, and comic books",
        options: ["predict","require","display","target"],
        correct_option: "display"
    },
    {
        question: "Before John got on the stage to give the speech, he took a deep ________ to calm himself down",
        options: ["order","rest","effort","breath"],
        correct_option: "breath"
    },
    {
        question: "Most young people in Taiwan are not satisfied with a high school _____ and continue to pursue further education in college",
        options: ["maturity","diploma","foundation","guarantee"],
        correct_option: "diploma"
    },
    {
        question: "Residents are told not to dump all household waste _____ into the trash can; reusable materials should first be sorted out and recycled",
        options: ["shortly","straight","forward","namely"],
        correct_option: "straight"
    },
    {
        question: "Kevin had been standing on a ladder trying to reach for a book on the top shelf when he lost his ______ and fell to the ground",
        options: ["volume","weight","balance","direction"],
        correct_option: "balance"
    },
    {
        question: "If student enrollment continues to drop, some programs at the university may be ______ to reduce the operation costs",
        options: ["relieved","eliminated","projected","accounted"],
        correct_option: "eliminated"
    },
    {
        question: "People in that remote village feed themselves by hunting and engaging in _____ forms of agriculture. No modern agricultural methods are used",
        options: ["universal","splendid","primitive","courteous"],
        correct_option: "primitive"
    },
    {
        question: "The government issued a travel _____ for Taiwanese in response to the outbreak of civil war in Syria",
        options: ["alert","monument","exit","circulation"],
        correct_option: "alert"
    },
    {
        question: "The baby panda Yuan Zai at the Taipei Zoo was separated from her mother because of a minor injury that occurred during her birth. She was ______ by zookeepers for a while",
        options: ["departed","jailed","tended","captured"],
        correct_option: "tended"
    },
  ]
  